[{"Date": "2020-04-26 09:08:28+00:00", "question": "Which correctly describes a sequence of events presented in the passage?", "option1": "Which correctly describes a sequence of events presented in the passage?", "option2": "Subprime mortgages lead to widespread defaults, which lead to landlord abandonment.", "option3": "Reverse redlining leads to landlord abandonment, which leads to the use of buildings for crime", "option4": "Redlining leads to reverse redlining, which leads to constrained access to health care, jobs,", "option5": "Landlord abandonment leads to redlining, which leads to crime and drug dealing.", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-04-26 09:08:28+00:00", "question": "Which of the following, not mentioned in the passage, would qualify as an example of reverse redlining as defined in the passage?", "option1": "A bank refuses to offer mortgages to consumers in certain neighborhoods.", "option2": "Police respond to reports of crimes more quickly in some neighborhoods than in others.", "option3": "A grocery store in a low-income neighborhood sells low-quality produce for high prices", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-04-26 09:08:27+00:00", "question": "The passage indicates that", "option1": "Large Nude in a Red Armchair conveyed a sensuous, rich mood.", "option2": "Matisse verbally commented about Woman with Yellow Hair.", "option3": "Matisse and Picasso were lifelong friends.", "option4": "Matisse worked on The Dream for nearly a decade.", "option5": "Matisse was older than Picasso.", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-04-26 09:08:27+00:00", "question": "According to the passage, which of the following describes Woman with Yellow Hair?", "option1": "It was parody of a work by Matisse.", "option2": "Its colors were not rigidly tied to its form.", "option3": "Its color palette was larger than that of The Dream.", "option4": "It was a response to a work by Matisse.", "option5": "It was harsh and grotesque.", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-04-26 09:08:27+00:00", "question": "The author would most likely agree with which of the following statements?", "option1": "Artistic rivalries are more like Olympic competitions than professional sports.", "option2": "Artistic mastery is best demonstrated by employing multiple styles.", "option3": "Artists must be good conversationalists.", "option4": "Artistic rivalries can actually be reciprocally nourishing.", "option5": "Artistic rivalries generally last for decades.", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-04-26 09:08:27+00:00", "question": "The primary purpose of the passage is to", "option1": "discuss the two best painters of an epoch.", "option2": "evaluate a theory and endorse a revision.", "option3": "compare selected works of two masters.", "option4": "show that Matisse's work is more sophisticated.", "option5": "illustrate how Picasso taught Matisse.", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-04-25 17:08:58+00:00", "question": "Ria, Pat and Max decided to participate in a race. Three of them go round a circular track in 4, 6, 8 hours. They start from the same point at the same time. Find how long will they take to be together at the place again?", "option1": "48", "option2": "24", "option3": "30", "option4": "32", "option5": "None of the above", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-04-25 16:12:08+00:00", "question": "Chloe wishes to distribute 348 mangoes and 232 oranges equally among a number of beggars, without mixing the oranges and the mangoes (that is a person either gets mangoes or oranges). Find the greatest number of fruits that a beggar can receive?", "option1": "232", "option2": "212", "option3": "234", "option4": "116", "option5": "None of the above", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-04-25 15:52:39+00:00", "question": "Find the largest 3 digit number which gives 7 as a remainder when divided by 17 and 19?", "option1": "966", "option2": "977", "option3": "976", "option4": "968", "option5": "None of the above", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-04-25 15:07:06+00:00", "question": "Camryn practices the trumpet every 11th day and the flute every 3rd day.\n\nCamryn practiced both the trumpet and the flute today.  How many days until Camryn practices the trumpet and flute again in the same day?", "option1": "30 days", "option2": "33 days", "option3": "34th", "option4": "36th", "option5": "None of the above", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-04-25 14:47:29+00:00", "question": "A student has gotten the following grades on his tests: 87, 95, 76, and 88. He wants an 85 or better overall. What is the minimum grade he must get on the last test in order to achieve that average?", "option1": "78", "option2": "79", "option3": "80", "option4": "81", "option5": "82", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-04-25 14:28:26+00:00", "question": "The average weight of a group of 30 friends increases by 1 kg when the weight of their football coach was added. If average weight of the group after including the weight of the football coach is 31 kg, what is the weight of their football coach?", "option1": "31 kg", "option2": "61 kg", "option3": "60 kg", "option4": "62 kg", "option5": "91 kg", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-04-25 14:18:11+00:00", "question": "A shopkeeper bought 30 kg of wheat at the rate of $45 per kg. He sold forty percent of the total quantity at the rate of $50 per kg. Approximately, at what price per kg, should he sell the remaining quantity to make 25 per cent overall profit?", "option1": "$54", "option2": "$52", "option3": "$50", "option4": "$60", "option5": "None of the above", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-04-25 14:09:51+00:00", "question": "Postcards costing 30 cents each and inland letters costing $1.50 each were purchased for $66. Total number of postcards and inland letters purchased was 60. If the number of postcards and inland letters is interchanged, then the cost is:", "option1": "$42", "option2": "$30", "option3": "$21", "option4": "$60", "option5": "None of the above", "Answer": "No answer given"}, {"Date": "2020-04-25 13:50:27+00:00", "question": "Student bought computer & printer. If he sold the computer @ 10% loss & printer @ 20% gain, he wont lose anything. If he sells computer @ 5% gain & the colour printer @ 15% loss, he would lose $800 in the bargain. How much did he pay for printer?", "option1": "$8000", "option2": "$16000", "option3": "$9000", "option4": "None of the above", "Answer": "No answer given"}]